A Guide to the Records of Julian A. Burruss, President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1906-1946
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series 7: Defense and the War Effort, 1940-1945
  - Virginia Defense Council, 7/1/1941-12/31/1941 (Box-folder 52-2606)
  - Virginia Defense Council, 1/1/1942-6/30/1942 (Box-folder 52-2607)
  - Bulletins issued by Virginia Defense Council, 1941-42 (Box-folder 52-2608)
  - Virginia Planning Board, 1941-42 (Box-folder 52-2609)
  - VPI Defense Measures, 1940-41 (2 folders) (Box-folder 52-2610 to 52-2611)
  - V.P.I. Defense Projects (Proposed by Departments), 1941 (Box-folder 52-2612)
  - Volunteer Offices (Box-folder 52-2613)
  - Voluntary Participation, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2614)
  - Volunteer Personnel Reports, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2615)
  - War & Navy, 1942 (Box-folder 52-2616)
  - War & Navy, 1943 (Box-folder 52-3617)
  - War & Navy-Directives, etc., 1943 (Box-folder 52-2618)
  - War Department, 1941-43 (Box-folder 52-2619)
  - War Production Board, 1945 (Box-folder 52-2620)
  - Wheeler, Frank H., Chief Air Raid Warden for VA, 1941 (Box-folder 52-2621)
- Oversize Folders
  - Geneology of names, Leftwich and Crawford (Box-folder 53-2622)
  - Orientation - Directions to New Students, 1930-37 (Box-folder 53-2623)
  - SIBOLD Matters, 1922 (Box-folder 53-2624)
    - Ejectment Case
    - Mrs. Anne Sibold sues VPI to recover one acre of land in the center of VPI she claims she is the sole heir. Includes 1874 copy of deed - James Hawley to Catherine and 1846 deed John, Mary, Alexander, Elizabeth Black to Charles Black.
  - Virginia Tech Organizational Chart #1 and Proposed Chart #2, 1919-21 (Folder 2625)